<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Application on Jashua R. White</title>
    <link>http://www.jashuawhite.com/tags/application/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Application on Jashua R. White</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 20:07:49 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.jashuawhite.com/tags/application/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Norris Jokes Machine</title>
      <link>http://www.jashuawhite.com/projects/chuck-norris-jokes-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 20:07:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jashuawhite.com/projects/chuck-norris-jokes-machine/</guid>
      <description>See the Pen Random Quote Machine by Jashua White (@jashuawhite) on CodePen.

Overview Through Freecodecamp, I was tasked with utilizing a quotes API of my choice to generate and display a random quote. I decided to play with it a bit and made a random joke generator by tapping into a Chuck Norris jokes API. The application allows for you to enter a custom name to be used in the jokes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Calculator</title>
      <link>http://www.jashuawhite.com/projects/javascript-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 20:07:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jashuawhite.com/projects/javascript-calculator/</guid>
      <description>See the Pen JavaScript MVC (Observer Pattern) Calculator by Jashua White (@jashuawhite) on CodePen.

Overview A Freecodecamp challenge that involved creating a basic JavaScript calculator. I chose to build the application out following the MVC design model. It was a great way to re-familiarize myself with MVC techniques and JavaScript&amp;rsquo;s object oriented design patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jefferson Health &amp; University</title>
      <link>http://www.jashuawhite.com/projects/jefferson-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 20:07:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jashuawhite.com/projects/jefferson-health/</guid>
      <description> 
Technology Stack  Adobe Experience Manager (AEM), CQ5, Adobe Target Custom AEM Components &amp;amp; Templates Java, JSP, HTL/Slightly, JCR API JavaScript, HTML, CSS jQuery, Bootstrap, Google Maps API, Google Analytics Eclipse, Maven, Git, Gitlab MailChimp, Healthgrades  Projects  Jefferson Health Jefferson University Jefferson University Hospitals Sidney Kimmel Cancer Center Jefferson Orthopedics Campaign Jefferson Health Knee Surgery Campaign  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>